[
	{"id":0,"question":"The angel woke up Peter in jail by doing what?","choices":[{"id":1,"text":"Hit him on the side"},{"id":2,"text":"Called his name"},{"id":3,"text":"Blew a trumpet"},{"id":3,"text":"Flung open the jail door"}],"answer":[{"id":1,"explanation":"Hit him on the side (Acts 12:7)"}]},
	{"id":1,"question":"How many seals does the scroll that only Jesus could open have in Revelation 5?","choices":[{"id":1,"text":"7"},{"id":2,"text":"6"},{"id":3,"text":"12"},{"id":3,"text":"1"}],"answer":[{"id":1,"explanation":"7 (Revelation 5:1)"}]},
	{"id":2,"question":"What instrument sounds the return of Jesus?","choices":[{"id":1,"text":"Trumpet"},{"id":2,"text":"Lyre"},{"id":3,"text":"Guitar"},{"id":3,"text":"Harp"}],"answer":[{"id":1,"explanation":"Trumpet (1 Thessalonians 4:16)"}]},
	{"id":3,"question":"How many books are in the New Testament?","choices":[{"id":1,"text":"27"},{"id":2,"text":"29"},{"id":3,"text":"36"},{"id":3,"text":"66"}],"answer":[{"id":1,"explanation":"27 (Matthew - Revelation)"}]},
	{"id":4,"question":"What type of insect did John the Baptist eat in the desert?","choices":[{"id":1,"text":"Locusts"},{"id":2,"text":"Bees"},{"id":3,"text":"Beetles"},{"id":3,"text":"Crickets"}],"answer":[{"id":1,"explanation":"Locusts (Matthew 3:4)"}]},
	{"id":5,"question":"Who were the first apostles called to follow Jesus?","choices":[{"id":1,"text":"Peter and Andrew"},{"id":2,"text":"James and John"},{"id":3,"text":"Philip and Nathanael"},{"id":3,"text":"Matthew and Thomas"}],"answer":[{"id":1,"explanation":"Peter and Andrew (Matthew 4:18-19 and John 1:42-43)"}]},
	{"id":6,"question":"After Jesus was arrested, which apostle disowned him three times?","choices":[{"id":1,"text":"Peter"},{"id":2,"text":"Judas"},{"id":3,"text":"John"},{"id":3,"text":"James"}],"answer":[{"id":1,"explanation":"Peter (Luke 22:59-62)"}]},
	{"id":7,"question":"Who recognized Jesus as the Messiah when he was presented at the Temple as a baby?","choices":[{"id":1,"text":"Simeon"},{"id":2,"text":"Eli"},{"id":3,"text":"King Herod"},{"id":3,"text":"Eleazar"}],"answer":[{"id":1,"explanation":"Simeon (Luke 2:25\u201335)"}]},
	{"id":8,"question":"Who asked Pilate for Jesus' body after the crucifixion?","choices":[{"id":1,"text":"Joseph of Arimathea"},{"id":2,"text":"Nicodemus"},{"id":3,"text":"Josephus"},{"id":3,"text":"Lazarus"}],"answer":[{"id":1,"explanation":"Joseph of Arimathea (John 19:38-42)"}]},
	{"id":9,"question":"Paul was shipwrecked on what island?","choices":[{"id":1,"text":"Malta"},{"id":2,"text":"Patmos"},{"id":3,"text":"Cyprus"},{"id":3,"text":"Patara"}],"answer":[{"id":1,"explanation":"Malta (Acts 28:1)"}]},
	{"id":10,"question":"What is the shortest book in the New Testament?","choices":[{"id":1,"text":"2 John"},{"id":2,"text":"1 John"},{"id":3,"text":"Jude"},{"id":3,"text":"James"}],"answer":[{"id":1,"explanation":"2 John"}]},
	{"id":11,"question":"Who is the author of the Book of Revelation?","choices":[{"id":1,"text":"John"},{"id":2,"text":"Luke"},{"id":3,"text":"Paul"},{"id":3,"text":"Author unknown"}],"answer":[{"id":1,"explanation":"John"}]},
	{"id":12,"question":"What was Matthew's profession before he became a disciple of Jesus?","choices":[{"id":1,"text":"Tax collector"},{"id":2,"text":"Fisherman"},{"id":3,"text":"Pharisee"},{"id":3,"text":"Tentmaker"}],"answer":[{"id":1,"explanation":"Tax collector (Matthew 9:9-13)"}]},
	{"id":13,"question":"To what city was Saul traveling when he encountered Jesus?","choices":[{"id":1,"text":"Damascus"},{"id":2,"text":"Emmaus"},{"id":3,"text":"Caesarea"},{"id":3,"text":"Sidon"}],"answer":[{"id":1,"explanation":"Damascus (Acts 9)"}]},
	{"id":14,"question":"Who was the first person to come upon the injured man in the parable of the Good Samaritan?","choices":[{"id":1,"text":"Priest"},{"id":2,"text":"Samaritan"},{"id":3,"text":"Rich man"},{"id":3,"text":"Pharisee"}],"answer":[{"id":1,"explanation":"Priest (Luke 10:29-37)"}]},
	{"id":15,"question":"In the Armour of God, the shield is called what?","choices":[{"id":1,"text":"Shield of Faith"},{"id":2,"text":"Shield of Salvation"},{"id":3,"text":"Shield of the Spirit"},{"id":3,"text":"Shield of Righteousness"}],"answer":[{"id":1,"explanation":"Shield of Faith (Ephesians 6:16)"}]},
	{"id":16,"question":"After Jesus fed people with 5 loaves of bread and 2 fish, how many baskets were left over?","choices":[{"id":1,"text":"12"},{"id":2,"text":"10"},{"id":3,"text":"3"},{"id":3,"text":"40"}],"answer":[{"id":1,"explanation":"12 (Matthew 14:20)"}]},
	{"id":17,"question":"What tribe is Paul from?","choices":[{"id":1,"text":"Benjamin"},{"id":2,"text":"Judah"},{"id":3,"text":"Levi"},{"id":3,"text":"Manasseh"}],"answer":[{"id":1,"explanation":"Benjamin (Philippians 3:5)"}]},
	{"id":18,"question":"According to the Beatitudes who will be filled?","choices":[{"id":1,"text":"Those who hunger and thirst for righteousness"},{"id":2,"text":"Those who eat the manna from heaven"},{"id":3,"text":"Those who eat the bread of life"},{"id":3,"text":"Those who wait on the Lord"}],"answer":[{"id":1,"explanation":"Those who hunger and thirst for righteousness (Matthew 5:6)"}]},
	{"id":19,"question":"By what name is Paul of Tarsus known before he begins his missionary activity?","choices":[{"id":1,"text":"Saul"},{"id":2,"text":"Solomon"},{"id":3,"text":"Paulos"},{"id":3,"text":"Paulus"}],"answer":[{"id":1,"explanation":"Saul (Acts 9:1)"}]},
	{"id":20,"question":"Who is the high priest of Jerusalem who put Jesus on trial?","choices":[{"id":1,"text":"Caiaphas"},{"id":2,"text":"Annas"},{"id":3,"text":"Eleazar"},{"id":3,"text":"Quirinius"}],"answer":[{"id":1,"explanation":"Caiaphas (John 11:49)"}]},
	{"id":21,"question":"In the Gospel According to John, which of the apostles doubted Jesus's resurrection?","choices":[{"id":1,"text":"Thomas"},{"id":2,"text":"Peter"},{"id":3,"text":"John"},{"id":3,"text":"Thaddeus"}],"answer":[{"id":1,"explanation":"Thomas (John 20:24-29)"}]},
	{"id":22,"question":"According to the Gospel of Matthew, where does Jesus's first public sermon take place?","choices":[{"id":1,"text":"On a mountainside"},{"id":2,"text":"In the Temple"},{"id":3,"text":"By the sea of Galilee"},{"id":3,"text":"In a boat"}],"answer":[{"id":1,"explanation":"On a mountainside (Matthew 5:1)"}]},
	{"id":23,"question":"How does Judas signal Jesus's identity to the Roman officials?","choices":[{"id":1,"text":"With a kiss"},{"id":2,"text":"By pointing his finger"},{"id":3,"text":"By nodding his head"},{"id":3,"text":"With a hug"}],"answer":[{"id":1,"explanation":"With a kiss (Luke 22:48)"}]},
	{"id":24,"question":"Who issued the orders to behead John the Baptist?","choices":[{"id":1,"text":"Herod Antipas"},{"id":2,"text":"Herod Archelaus"},{"id":3,"text":"Herod the Great"},{"id":3,"text":"Herod Agrippa"}],"answer":[{"id":1,"explanation":"Herod Antipas (Matthew 14:1&9-10)"}]},
	{"id":25,"question":"Which Gospel is written by a doctor?","choices":[{"id":1,"text":"Luke"},{"id":2,"text":"Matthew"},{"id":3,"text":"Mark"},{"id":3,"text":"John"}],"answer":[{"id":1,"explanation":"Luke (Colossians 4:14)"}]},
	{"id":26,"question":"Which book tells about the visit of the Wise men to baby Jesus?","choices":[{"id":1,"text":"Matthew"},{"id":2,"text":"Mark"},{"id":3,"text":"Luke"},{"id":3,"text":"John"}],"answer":[{"id":1,"explanation":"Matthew (Matthew 2)"}]},
	{"id":27,"question":"Who wrote the book of Acts?","choices":[{"id":1,"text":"Luke"},{"id":2,"text":"Peter"},{"id":3,"text":"Paul"},{"id":3,"text":"John"}],"answer":[{"id":1,"explanation":"Luke (Luke 1:3, Acts 1:1)"}]},
	{"id":28,"question":"How many wise and foolish girls were in Jesus' parable?","choices":[{"id":1,"text":"10"},{"id":2,"text":"5"},{"id":3,"text":"12"},{"id":3,"text":"3"}],"answer":[{"id":1,"explanation":"10 (Matthew 5:1)"}]},
	{"id":29,"question":"What did Jesus heal Bartimaeus of?","choices":[{"id":1,"text":"Blindness"},{"id":2,"text":"Leprosy"},{"id":3,"text":"Death"},{"id":3,"text":"Paraplegia"}],"answer":[{"id":1,"explanation":"Blindness (Mark 10:46-52)"}]},
	{"id":30,"question":"How many days was Lazarus in the tomb when Jesus brought him back to life?","choices":[{"id":1,"text":"4"},{"id":2,"text":"3"},{"id":3,"text":"2"},{"id":3,"text":"1"}],"answer":[{"id":1,"explanation":"4 (John 11:17)"}]},
	{"id":31,"question":"Who came to Jesus at night?","choices":[{"id":1,"text":"Nicodemus"},{"id":2,"text":"A rich young ruler"},{"id":3,"text":"Joseph of Arimathea"},{"id":3,"text":"The wise men"}],"answer":[{"id":1,"explanation":"Nicodemus (John 3:2)"}]},
	{"id":32,"question":"Which angel appeared to Mary?","choices":[{"id":1,"text":"Gabriel"},{"id":2,"text":"Michael"},{"id":3,"text":"Angel of the Lord"},{"id":3,"text":"Raphael"}],"answer":[{"id":1,"explanation":"Gabriel (Luke 1:26)"}]},
	{"id":33,"question":"The age of Jesus when He started His ministry?","choices":[{"id":1,"text":"30"},{"id":2,"text":"17"},{"id":3,"text":"41"},{"id":3,"text":"27"}],"answer":[{"id":1,"explanation":"30 (Luke 3:23)"}]},
	{"id":34,"question":"The man Jesus referred to as a 'fox'?","choices":[{"id":1,"text":"Herod"},{"id":2,"text":"Judas Iscariot"},{"id":3,"text":"Caesar"},{"id":3,"text":"Zebedee"}],"answer":[{"id":1,"explanation":"Herod (13:31-32)"}]},
	{"id":35,"question":"The criminal who was released by by Pilate, rather than Jesus?","choices":[{"id":1,"text":"Barabbas"},{"id":2,"text":"Barnabas"},{"id":3,"text":"Bartholomew"},{"id":3,"text":"Judas"}],"answer":[{"id":1,"explanation":"Barabbas (Mark 15:15)"}]},
	{"id":36,"question":"What was Barnabas' original name?","choices":[{"id":1,"text":"Joses"},{"id":2,"text":"Simon"},{"id":3,"text":"Matthew"},{"id":3,"text":"Laban"}],"answer":[{"id":1,"explanation":"Joses (Acts 4:36)"}]},
	{"id":37,"question":"What was the body of water Jesus calmed storms on two different occasions?","choices":[{"id":1,"text":"Sea of Galilee"},{"id":2,"text":"Dead Sea"},{"id":3,"text":"Mediterranean Sea"},{"id":3,"text":"Caspian Sea"}],"answer":[{"id":1,"explanation":"Sea of Galilee (Matthew 8 & Matthew 14)"}]},
	{"id":38,"question":"What centurion was a follower of Jesus Christ?","choices":[{"id":1,"text":"Cornelius"},{"id":2,"text":"Archipus"},{"id":3,"text":"Demetrius"},{"id":3,"text":"Urbanus"}],"answer":[{"id":1,"explanation":"Cornelius (Acts 10)"}]},
	{"id":39,"question":"Who replaced Judas Iscariot?","choices":[{"id":1,"text":"Mathias"},{"id":2,"text":"Paul"},{"id":3,"text":"Silas"},{"id":3,"text":"Barsabas"}],"answer":[{"id":1,"explanation":"Mathias (Acts 1:15-26)"}]},
	{"id":40,"question":"Who was the mother of John the Baptist?","choices":[{"id":1,"text":"Elizabeth"},{"id":2,"text":"Mary Magdalene"},{"id":3,"text":"Salome"},{"id":3,"text":"Anna"}],"answer":[{"id":1,"explanation":"Elizabeth (Luke 1)"}]},
	{"id":41,"question":"Which disciple was the brother of Andrew?","choices":[{"id":1,"text":"Peter"},{"id":2,"text":"Thomas"},{"id":3,"text":"James"},{"id":3,"text":"Philip"}],"answer":[{"id":1,"explanation":"Peter (John 1:40)"}]},
	{"id":42,"question":"Who asked Jesus the question, \"What is truth\"?","choices":[{"id":1,"text":"Pontius Pilate"},{"id":2,"text":"Herod"},{"id":3,"text":"Caiaphas"},{"id":3,"text":"Cesar Augustus"}],"answer":[{"id":1,"explanation":"Pontius Pilate (John 18:38)"}]},
	{"id":43,"question":"Who was raised from the dead in the city of Joppa?","choices":[{"id":1,"text":"Dorcas"},{"id":2,"text":"Jairus' Daughter"},{"id":3,"text":"Eutychus"},{"id":3,"text":"Agabus"}],"answer":[{"id":1,"explanation":"Dorcas (Acts 9:36-42)"}]},
	{"id":44,"question":"Which Gospel mentions Rahab and Ruth in its genealogy?","choices":[{"id":1,"text":"Matthew"},{"id":2,"text":"Mark"},{"id":3,"text":"Luke"},{"id":3,"text":"John"}],"answer":[{"id":1,"explanation":"Matthew (Matthew 1:5)"}]},
	{"id":45,"question":"What city were the Jesus followers first called Christians?","choices":[{"id":1,"text":"Antioch"},{"id":2,"text":"Jerusalem"},{"id":3,"text":"Damascus"},{"id":3,"text":"Ephesus"}],"answer":[{"id":1,"explanation":"Antioch (Acts 11:26)"}]}
]